Guide to the Zaki Nusseibeh Collection of photographs AD.MC.020
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with Prince Charles and Zaki Nusseibeh (center) on the occasion of The Queen's Diamond Jubilee., 2012; ref64; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Chandeliers; London, England, UK; Royalty; Men; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Color Photography; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-
- Sheikh Zayed with Prince Charles and Princess Diana on a red carpet with Zaki Nusseibeh (second from the left, wearing a dark suit)., 1989; ref65; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Royalty; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Bags/Purses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Weapons; Guns; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-; Diana, Princess of Wales, 1961-1997
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., 1979; ref66; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Royalty; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Canes/Walking Sticks; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-2022
- Sheikh Zayed, Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh (center) at a dinner hosted by Sheikh Zayed in honor of Queen Elizabeth at Claridge Hotel., 1989; ref67; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; London, England, UK; Royalty; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Men; Women; Medals/Insignia; Jewelry; Hotels; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-2022
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., 1979; ref68; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Royalty; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Gloves; Bags/Purses; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-2022
- Sheikh Zayed, Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh (background, wearing a suit) with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher., 1981; ref69; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Men; Women; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990; Thatcher, Margaret, 1925-2013
- Sheikh Zayed and Queen Elizabeth, with Prince Philip, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh (second from the left)., 1989; ref70; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; London, England, UK; Color Photography; Men; Women; Royalty; Palaces; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-2022; Philip, Prince, consort of Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1921-2021
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan and Prince Charles holding a gift with Zaki Nusseibeh (far right) and Ahmed Jumaa Al Zaabi., 1989; ref71; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Royalty; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with Prince Charles walking on a deck of the Royal Yacht Britannia with Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed (with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background)., 1989; ref72; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Color Photography; Boats/Ships; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Bow Ties; Political Leadership; Transportation; Group Portraits; Royalty; Charles III, King of Great Britain, 1948-; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (center) greeting British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher during her visit to UAE., 1981; ref73; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Color Photography; Cars/Trucks; Political Leadership; Transportation; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Thatcher, Margaret, 1925-2013
- Sheikh Zayed, Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh (background, between Thatcher and Zayed) with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher., 1981; ref74; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1912-1990; Thatcher, Margaret, 1925-2013
- Sheikh Zayed with Indira Gandhi and Zaki Nusseibeh (center, leaning over the chair)., February 1975; ref75; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Regional/National Dress; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Furnishings; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Gandhi, Indira (Priyadarshini), 1917-1984
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right) covered in flower petals during a trip to India., February 1975; ref76; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Men; India; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Microphones; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed seated next to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto with Zaki Nusseibeh taking notes (front, right)., Circa 1970; ref77; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Men; Political Leadership; Pens/Inkwells; Furnishings; Audio cassette; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with President Fakhruddin Ali Ahmed and Zaki Nusseibeh (center, wearing a tie) in the middle., 1975; ref78; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Cameras; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Fakhruddin Ali, Ahmed, 1905-1977
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right of Sheikh Zayed) walking in front of the Great Gate of Taj Mahal., February 1975; ref79; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Political Leadership; Photographic Prints; Agra, India; Color Photography; Men; Uniforms; Architecture; Buildings; Military/Soldiers; Regional/National Dress; Monuments/Memorials; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (front row, left of Sheikh Zayed) with a crowd gathered around a red motorcycle during India visit., February 1975; ref80; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Men; Crowds; Motorcycles; Color Photography; Military/Soldiers; Transportation; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right) walking in front of the Hauz Khas Pavillions., February 1975; ref81; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Monuments/Memorials; Color Photography; Architecture; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Delhi, India; Monuments/Memorials; Outdoors; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right) covered in flower petals during a visit to India., February 1975; ref82; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Color Photography; Men; Microphones; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right) covered in yellow flower petals during a visit to India., February 1975; ref83; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; India; Color Photography; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed talking to reporters next to Zaki Nusseibeh (far right) during his visit to the Aligarh Muslim University., February 1975; ref84; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Political Leadership; Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh, India; Men; Microphones; Color Photography; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Universities; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Zaki Nusseibeh (left of Sheikh Zayed) and a group of men in front of The Iron Pillar of Delhi., February 1975; ref85; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Monuments/Memorials; Color Photography; Men; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Delhi, India; Outdoors; Monuments/Memorials; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with a man., Circa 1970; ref86; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed wearing flower garlands, walking next to men., Circa 1970; ref87; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Outdoors; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed standing on a stage during a visit to India with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., February 1975; ref88; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Men; Military/Soldiers; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Tents; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (pointing, front and center) gathered around an architectural model display of a mosque., Circa 1970; ref89; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Architecture; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed next to Zulfikar Ali Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh (left)., Circa 1974; ref90; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Political Leadership; Men; Medals/Insignia; Regional/National Dress; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Group portrait of Sheikh Zayed, Zulfikar Ali Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., Circa 1974; ref91; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed holding a child, with a crowd gathered around them (including Zaki Nusseibeh on the right)., Circa 1970; ref92; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Men; Crowds; Children; Girls; Military/Soldiers; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (far right) with Benazir Bhutto are greeted with flowers., Circa 1990; ref93; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Political Leadership; Children; Girls; Boys; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Bhutto, Benazir, 1953-2007
- Sheikh Zayed with Benazir Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh (center, behind Zayed and Bhutto) in front of a UAE airplane (linked Ref95)., Circa 1990; ref94; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Airplanes; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Bhutto, Benazir, 1953-2007
- Sheikh Zayed with Benazir Bhutto and Zaki Nusseibeh (center, behind Zayed and Bhutto) in front of a UAE airplane (linked Ref94)., Circa 1990; ref95; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Pakistan; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Airplanes; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Bhutto, Benazir, 1953-2007
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (second from the left) with a group of men at the opening of the reception hall at the Pakistan Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology., 9 May 1972; ref96; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Islamabad, Pakistan; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed talking to reporters at a desk with Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh on the right., Circa 1970; ref97; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Microphones; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1961-
- Sheikh Zayed standing beside a commemorative plaque for Sheikh Zayed Women's Hospital Larkana next to Zaki Nusseibeh (far right)., 12 March 1974; ref98; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Hospitals; English Writing; Women; Larkana, Pakistan; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed wearing a dagger with Khalifa bin Hamad Al Thani., 1969; ref99; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Police; Cars/Trucks; Swords/Knives; Regional/National Dress; Weapons; Transportation; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Portrait of Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970; ref100; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Swords/Knives; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Weapons; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nahyan and men., Circa 1970; ref101; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Flags; Buildings; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Hamdan bin Mohammed Al Nayhan, Sheikh, c.1930s-1989
- A collage of Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; ref102; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Birds; Children; Boys; Individual Portraits; Animals; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019
- A portrait of Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan., Circa 1970; ref103; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Clocks/Watches; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019
- Sheikh Zayed holding a falcon., Circa 1970; ref104; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Birds; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Arabic Calligraphy; Drinks/Beverages; Art; Political Leadership; Men; Individual Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and Abd Al Jalil Mohammed Al Fahim with a falcon and a group of men., Circa 1970; ref105; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Animals; Birds; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Drinks/Beverages; Electricity; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with Sheikh Maktoum Al Maktoum and Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan and other men., Circa 1970; ref106; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Maktoum bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1943-2006
- Sheikh Zayed holding a falcon sitting next to a man., Circa 1970; ref107; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Animals; Birds; Arabic Calligraphy; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Books; Art; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with soldiers at a memorial with Zaki Nusseibeh in the back., Circa 1990; ref108; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Military/Soldiers; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Uniforms; Monuments/Memorials; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed at an event., Circa 1970; ref109; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Audiences/Spectators; Events/Occasions; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Cameras; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with Chad President Ngarta Tombalbaye, with Zaki Nusseibeh standing on the left., Circa 1970; ref110; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Cigarettes; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Tombalbaye, Ngarta, 1918-1975
- Zaki Nusseibeh (bottom right, above the man wearing glasses) in a crowd of leaders and dignitaries., Circa 1970; ref111; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Turbans
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with a man with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., Circa 1970; ref112; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Turbans; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed sitting next to a man in front of Zaki Nusseibeh (right)., Circa 1970; ref113; Studio Elias Jamoua (UAE/Iraq); 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Senegal President Léopold Sédar Senghor and Zaki Nusseibeh (left of Sheikh Zayed, wearing a tie)., 7 November 1975; ref114; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Senghor, Léopold Sédar, 1906-2001
- Sheikh Zayed walking with President of Zaire Mobutu Sese Seko and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., Circa 1970; ref115; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Furnishings; Chandeliers; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mobutu Sese Seko (Kuku Ngbendu Wa Za Banga), 1930-1997
- Sheikh Zayed seated next to Somali President Siyaad Barre, with Zaki Nusseibeh on the far left., Circa 1970; ref116; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Siyaad Barre, Maxamed, 1920-1995